<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="sling:OsgiConfig"
    attestation.email.template="/etc/notification/email/html/dotcom/content_expiry_email_template.html"
    attestationDays.email.description="The Digital Governance team is conducting a web page content review and attestation for your designated web pages. The goal of this review is to facilitate current and accurate content on your web pages. If you are not the correct Reviewer or have questions, please send an email to the  ${attestationEmail}  mailbox as soon as possible.  The instructions and checklist for completing the review and attestation are attached to this email. If changes to your web pages are needed during this review, please follow your normal content management request and approval process.  You have 21 days to click through all pages, links, articles, etc., submit any requests for needed changes, and perform the Content Attestation Signoff within AEM.  "
    attestationDays.email.id="digitalattestation@suntrust.com"
    attestationDays.email.note="PLEASE NOTE: This attestation has an automated escalation process and will email your direct Manager, if the attestation is not completed by the deadline."
    attestationDays.email.subject=" [STAGE]Content Attestation-ACTION REQUIRED"
    noOfWeekAdvance="2"
    noOfWeekAdvance.email.description="Digital Governance is conducting a web page content review and attestation for SunTrust.com and all related web pages. The goal of this review is to ensure that all client facing content on SunTrust.com is accurate. If you are receiving this notification, you are assigned as a reviewer for one or more web pages. The content review and attestation process for your assigned web pages will begin in ${attestationWeek} weeks. You will receive an additional email notification to begin the review process. You will have 21 days from the start date to click through all pages, links, articles, etc., submit any request forms for needed changes, and perform the content attestation signoff within AEM. If changes to your web pages are needed during this review, please follow your regular content management request and approval process. Digital Governance will provide online training that details the necessary steps in your review and to answer any questions you may have regarding this effort. Click here to view the digital inventory.  "
    noOfWeekAdvance.email.id="digitalattestation@suntrust.com"
    noOfWeekAdvance.email.note="If you have any questions, please send an email to the Digital Attestations mailbox at  ${attestationEmail}  Thank you."
    noOfWeekAdvance.email.subject="Content Attestation-Notification"
    noOfWeekDue="2"
    noOfWeekDue.email.description="The Content Attestation process for the below web area(s) is underway with 1 week remaining, and requires your review. The goal of this review is to facilitate current and accurate content on your web pages. The instructions and checklist for completing the review and attestation are attached. If changes to your web pages are needed during this review, please follow your normal content management request and approval process. The request number should be entered along with your attestation.You will have 1 week from today to click through all pages, links, articles, etc., submit any request forms for needed changes, and perform the Content Attestation Signoff within AEM. "
    noOfWeekDue.email.id="digitalattestation@suntrust.com"
    noOfWeekDue.email.note="PLEASE NOTE: This attestation has an automated escalation process and will email your direct Manager, if the attestation is not completed by the deadline."
    noOfWeekDue.email.subject=" [STAGE]-Content Attestation -ACTION REQUIRED Reminder"
    noOfWeekOverdue="4"
    noOfWeekOverdue.email.description="The Content Attestation process for the below web area(s) is now 1 week overdue and requires your immediate attention. The goal of this review is to facilitate current and accurate content on your web pages. The reviewer (copied on this email) has not completed the content attestation within the attestation timeframe. The following notices were emailed to the reviewer: - Kickoff email, stating the timing of 20 days to perform the review and describing the automated escalation email process - Reminder email sent two weeks after the start date - Escalation email sent to the reviewer's direct manager and/or business owner (with the reviewer on copy) on the day after the due date (1 week ago) "
    noOfWeekOverdue.email.id="digitalattestation@suntrust.com"
    noOfWeekOverdue.email.note="Please reach out to the assigned reviewer to coordinate completion of this task within 2 business days. If the assigned reviewer is not available to complete the attestation, please designate a new reviewer and forward the contact name to the ${attestationEmail} mailbox."
    noOfWeekOverdue.email.subject=" [STAGE]-Content Attestation -1 WEEK OVERDUE"
    noOfWeekPast="3"
    noOfWeekPast.email.description="The Content Attestation process for your assigned web area(s) requires your immediate attention. The goal of this review is to facilitate current and accurate content on your web pages. The reviewer copied on this email, was given 20 days from the start date of the review to perform a detailed content review and submit needed change requests, and this review has not been completed in AEM. Please reach out to the assigned reviewer to coordinate completion of this task within 5 business days. If the assigned reviewer is not available to complete the attestation, please designate a new reviewer and forward the contact name to the 'Digital Attestation' mailbox. "
    noOfWeekPast.email.id="digitalattestation@suntrust.com"
    noOfWeekPast.email.note="Please contact the ${attestationEmail} shared mailbox if you have concerns with completing this review.."
    noOfWeekPast.email.subject=" [STAGE]-Content Attestation -OVERDUE"
    onUp.root.path="[]"
    sites.list="[suntrust,onUp,suntrustrh]"
    suntrust.attestation.csv.path="/content/dam/dotcom/en-us/suntrust/configuration/attestation_owner.csv"
    suntrust.attestation.model.path="/etc/workflow/models/dotcom/content-expiry-owner-notification-workflow/jcr:content/model"
    suntrust.cc.email.dl="DL.STEL.Draw.Process@SunTrust.com"
    suntrust.digital.attestation.emailid="digitalattestation_test@suntrust.com"
    suntrust.root.path="[/content/suntrust/dotcom]"
    suntrust.sender.displayName="Digital Attestation"
    suntrust.sender.emailid="DigitalAttestation@SunTrust.com"
    suntrustrh.root.path="[]"
    workflow.payload.path="/content/suntrust/dotcom"/>
